Chrome Touch would enable you to scroll on a webpage by simply using a touch interface.

Chrome Touch 可以实现用鼠标拖动来滑动整个页面, 就像使用iPod Touch或iPhone一样。

* On the normal text and Textarea form, the scrolling command do not run. You can select text normally.
* 设置为"自动"模式时, 自动识别并忽略网页文本, 你可以正常选择文本。

* To turning off the scrolling feature temporarily, press Ctrl or Shift key while dragging.
* 设置为"完整"模式时, 在鼠标拖动时按Ctrl或Shift键可临时关闭此功能以便于选择文本。

***************************
chromeTouch 设置

Basic 基本设置

Touch Mode 模式

Auto(no dragging on text) 自动(可以正常选择文本)
Full(dragging anytime)       完整(滑动整个页面)
off (no dragging)               关闭

use Easy Swith 模式切换
Hot key 热键

Press Hot Key, 按热键

Touch Mode will change 'Auto'->'Full'->'Off'->... 
模式将在'自动'->'完整'->'关闭'之间循环设定。

don't show icon 不显示地址栏图标

Use Mouse Button 鼠标键设置

Left Button 左键
Middle Button 中键
Right Button 右键

Drag Direction 拖动方向设置

Normal 正常
Reverse 反向

***************************

Drag and Sliding Parameter 参数设置

Drag Speed 拖动速度

Change faster or slower the screen scroll than the mouse drag speed.
相对于鼠标拖动速度,网页的滑动速度。

fast 快
slow 慢
default 默认

Sliding Distance 滑动距离

The screen slides according to the drag speed when the mouse button is up after the drag. The length of the sliding factor.
每次鼠标拖动操作,网页滑动的距离。

short 短
long 长
default 默认

Sliding Factor 滑动系数

Sliding speed is reduced gradually until stop. Sliding brake factor.
设置制动距离。

fast end 快速制动
slow end 缓慢制动
default 默认
Never stop  无制动

***************************

Other Features 其它设置

Bounce Effect 网页回弹效果

This is an effect that the screen rebounds to the windows after it slides the uppermost part or the under the screen。
启用后, 网页滑动到窗口顶端或底端时, 将弹回一点。

on 启用

No scrolllbars mode 取消垂直滚动条

You can use the screen more widely by the mode. 让你的屏幕更宽一点 :)

Enable keyboard navigation 启用键盘导航
Enable mouse wheel 启用鼠标滚轮

on 启用

Mouse Gesture 鼠标手势
Drag the page left for page back, drag right for page forward.
向左拖动网页后退, 向右拖动网页前进

Reverse gesture direction for forward/back page
反向操作: 向左则前进, 向右则后退

on 启用